ACTWU Newsclipping Files regarding J.P. Stevens Boycott 5744
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- Two Articles from The Catholic Weekly and The Montgomery Advertiser, 1977; News clipping (Box 2, Folder 52)
  - Item 1: Atlanta Province Passes Resolutions... Labor and Death Penalty, 1977; News clipping (Box 2, Folder 52)
    Catholic Weekly. February 27, 1977
  - Item 2: The Stevens Battle, 1977; News clipping (Box 2, Folder 52)
    Montgomery Advertiser. March 11, 1977
- The Struggle for Human Decency Gains a Rising Tide of Support, 1978; News clipping (Box 2, Folder 53)
  IUD Viewpoint. First Quarter, 1978
- Labor, Civil Rights, Clergy Join: Boycott Launched for Economic Justice, 1977; News clipping (Box 2, Folder 54)
  New York Teacher. March 6, 1977
- The U.S. Catholic Conference Reports to Southern Bishops on J. P. Stevens Labor Issue, 1977; News clipping (Box 2, Folder 55)
  The Catholic Weekly. February 27, 1977
- Two Articles from The Greenville News and Advertising Age, 1977; News clipping (Box 2, Folder 56)
  - Item 1: AFL-CIO Textile Drive to be Based in Charlotte, 1977; News clipping (Box 2, Folder 56)
    The Greenville News. February 24, 1977
  - Item 2: Clothing Union ad takes on Stevens, 1978; News clipping (Box 2, Folder 56)
    Advertising Age. March 14, 1977
- The Devious Battle for the Sunbelt, 1977; News clipping (Box 2, Folder 57)
  Ashland Times-Gazette. February 16, 1977
- J. P. Stevens Staff, 1977; News clipping (Box 2, Folder 58)
  February 10, 1977.
- J. P. Stevens Annual Stockholders Meeting, 1977; News clipping (Box 2, Folder 59)
  Statement by Mrs. Martin Luther King, Jr. March 1, 1977
- Boycott J. P. Stevens Textile Products, 1977; News clipping (Box 2, Folder 60)
  American Teacher. March 1977
- Protest Marks Stevens Meeting, 1977; News clipping (Box 2, Folder 61)
  The Greenville News. March 2, 1977
- Stevens' Rift With Union May Widen, 1977; News clipping (Box 2, Folder 62)
  The Journal of Commerce. March 3, 1977
- Taking Care of Business, 1977; News clipping (Box 2, Folder 63)
  The New Times. March 4, 1977
- The Struggle for Economic Justice at J. P. Stevens, 1977; News clipping (Box 2, Folder 64)
- J. P. Stevens Blasted at Company Meeting, 1977; News clipping (Box 2, Folder 65)
  AFL-CIO News. March 5, 1977
- I enclose a letter sent to Mr. Burt Beck, 1976; News clipping (Box 2, Folder 66)
  Letter from Abram Lerner, Director of the Hirshhorn Museum and Sculpture Garden, To Charles English, Vice-President of ACWA. March 9, 1977
- Two Articles from RWDSU Record and the Detroit AFL-CIO News, 1977; News clipping (Box 2, Folder 67)
  - Item 1: Sees Need for Coalition to Topple J. P. Stevens, 1977; News clipping (Box 2, Folder 67)
    RWDSU Record. March 1977
  - Item 2: Don't Buy These J. P. Stevens Products, 1977; News clipping (Box 2, Folder 67)
    Detroit AFL-CIO News. March 10, 1977
- Stevens Boycotters March On Annual Meeting, 1977; News clipping (Box 2, Folder 68)
  The Guild Reporter. March 11, 1977
- Stevens Digs Its Heels In Deeper, 1977; News clipping (Box 2, Folder 69)
  Business Week. March 14, 1977
- Four Articles from various newspapers., 1977; News clipping (Box 2, Folder 70)
  - Item 1: Small Town Now a Symbolic Battle Ground For Textile Union, 1977; News clipping (Box 2, Folder 70)
    Chicago Tribune. March 14, 1977
  - Item 2: Sixty Minutes May Televise Story, 1977; News clipping (Box 2, Folder 70)
    Roanoke Rapids Herald. March 13, 1977
  - Item 3: NLRB Seeks Injunction Against J. P. Stevens Co., 1977; News clipping (Box 2, Folder 70)
    The Miami Herald. March 18, 1977
  - Item 4: Textile Union to Draft Southern Wage Policy, 1977; News clipping (Box 2, Folder 70)
    Winston- Salem Journal. March 12, 1977
- Eighteen Articles from various newspapers, 1977; News clipping (Box 2, Folder 71)
  - Item 1: Clothing Union Ad Takes On Stevens, 1977; News clipping (Box 2, Folder 71)
  - Item 2: Priests Support Boycott, 1977; News clipping (Box 2, Folder 71)
    Southern Cross. February 24, 1977
  - Item 3: Hearing Set On Injunction Against JPS, 1977; News clipping (Box 2, Folder 71)
    Roanoke Rapids Herald. March 20, 1977
  - Item 4: Fierce Southern Union Push A Result of Many Changes, News clipping (Box 2, Folder 71)
    New York Times.
  - Item 5: Union's Comparisons Criticized, 1977; News clipping (Box 2, Folder 71)
    Greenville Piedmont. March 14, 1977
  - Item 6: Boycotts Wielded As Key Weapon In Union Arsenal, 1977; News clipping (Box 2, Folder 71)
    The Commercial Appeal. March 20, 1977
  - Item 7: Mikulski Hits Importation, Big Business, 1977; News clipping (Box 2, Folder 71)
    The News American. March 24, 1977
  - Item 8: The Amalgamated Clothing and Textiles Workers Union, 1977; News clipping (Box 2, Folder 71)
    Lenoir News-Topic. March 15, 1977
  - Item 9: Getting the Right To Unionize, 1977; News clipping (Box 2, Folder 71)
    Daily Californian. March 4, 1977
  - Item 10: ACTWU Proposes Pay Hike Immediately, 1977; News clipping (Box 2, Folder 71)
    Roanoke Rapids Herald. March 18, 1977
  - Item 11: AFL-CIO Boycotts, 1977; News clipping (Box 2, Folder 71)
    Labor News. March 17, 1977
  - Item 12: JPSEEC Request Denied Again, 1977; News clipping (Box 2, Folder 71)
  - Item 13: South's Labor Changes Spark Big Union Push, 1977; News clipping (Box 2, Folder 71)
    The Atlanta Journal and The Atlanta Constitution. March 20, 1977
  - Item 14: J. P. Stevens Target of Leaflet Blitz, 1977; News clipping (Box 2, Folder 71)
    News and Views. February 1977
  - Item 15: Labor Claims Gains In Slow Southern State Drive, 1977; News clipping (Box 2, Folder 71)
    The Dallas Morning News. March 17, 1977
  - Item 16: Unions Here Urge Boycott Of Textiles, 1977; News clipping (Box 2, Folder 71)
    The Pittsburgh Press. March 16, 1977
  - Item 17: Church Council Errs Seriously On Stevens, 1977; News clipping (Box 2, Folder 71)
    Greenville Piedmont. March 7, 1977
  - Item 18: Stike photograph., News clipping (Box 2, Folder 71)
- Three Articles from various newspapers, 1977; News clipping (Box 2, Folder 72)
  - Item 1: 3 Lead Boycott Of Stevens Co., 1977; News clipping (Box 2, Folder 72)
    Waterbury American. February 28, 1977
  - Item 2: Labor to Fight, 1977; News clipping (Box 2, Folder 72)
    Pittsburgh Post-Gazette. March 16, 1977
  - Item 3: NLRB Seeks Injunction Against Firm, 1977; News clipping (Box 2, Folder 72)
    Newsday. March 18, 1977
- Five Articles from various newspapers, 1977; News clipping (Box 2, Folder 73)
  - Item 1: NLRB Seeks Injunction, 1977; News clipping (Box 2, Folder 73)
    The Boston Globe. March 18, 1977
  - Item 2: Booklet Defends Stevens Policies, 1977; News clipping (Box 2, Folder 73)
    Roanoke Rapids Herald. March 11, 1977
  - Item 3: Union Leaders Back Stevens Firm Boycott, 1977; News clipping (Box 2, Folder 73)
    The Indianapolis Star. March 16, 1977
  - Item 4: Union Seeks Textile Wage Hikes, 1977; News clipping (Box 2, Folder 73)
    The State. March 15, 1977
  - Item 5: AFL-CIO Rates Textile Boycott As Top Concern, 1977; News clipping (Box 2, Folder 73)
    The Fort Worth Star-Telegram. March 16, 1977
- Bishops Urge Stevens 'Neutrality', 1978; News clipping (Box 2, Folder 74)
  Indianapolis Criterion. March 17, 1978
- Diocesan Position Favors Boycott of Stevens Textiles, 1978; News clipping (Box 2, Folder 75)
  Little Rock Guardian. March 17, 1978
- J. P. Stevens Faces the Music, 1978; News clipping (Box 2, Folder 76)
  Valley Advocate. March 22, 1978
- Bradley to Keynote Film on J. P. Stevens Struggle, 1977; News clipping (Box 2, Folder 77)
  The Los Angeles Citizen. March 25, 1977
- Emancipation From Meany: New Life For The Unions, 1977; News clipping (Box 2, Folder 78)
  The Nation. March 26, 1977
- Labor In The South: The Stonewall At Stevens, 1978; News clipping (Box 2, Folder 79)
  Commonweal. March 31, 1977
- Three Articles from various newspapers, 1977; News clipping (Box 2, Folder 80)
  - Item 1: Textile Union Asks 'Substantial' Pay Hikes, 1977; News clipping (Box 2, Folder 80)
    The Charlotte Observer. March 15, 1977
  - Item 2: Garment Workers In Pottsville Area March To Protest Imports, 1977; News clipping (Box 2, Folder 80)
    Pottsville Republican. April 12, 1977
  - Item 3: J. P. Stevens Hit With New Labor Charges, 1977; News clipping (Box 2, Folder 80)
    Federation News. February 1977
- A Touch of Civil Rights Fervor, 1977; News clipping (Box 2, Folder 81)
  Time Magazine. March 14, 1977
- J. P. Stevvens Doesn't Come to Terms With Organized Labor: Trouble Looming, 1977; News clipping (Box 2, Folder 82)
  The New Republic. March 12, 1977
- Union 'Spectacular' Scheduled for WNY, 1977; News clipping (Box 2, Folder 83)
  Buffalo Evening News. March 12, 1977
- Labor: Squeezing Stevens, 1978; News clipping (Box 2, Folder 84)
  Newsweek. March 6, 1977
- J. P. Stevens Co. and the Boycott, 1977; News clipping (Box 2, Folder 85)
  New Republic. March 5, 1977
- J. P. Stevens Reports Decline in Earnings At Hostile Meeting, 1977; News clipping (Box 2, Folder 86)
  Wall Street Journal. March 2, 1977
- Please don't buy J. P. Stevens Products, 1977; News clipping (Box 2, Folder 87)
  Steel Labor. March 1977
- Guild in Anti-Stevens Demonstration, 1977; News clipping (Box 2, Folder 88)
  Frontpage. March 1977
- The Struggle for Economic Justice at J. P. Stevens, 1977; News clipping (Box 2, Folder 89)
  Voice. March 1977
- Three Articles from various newspapers, 1977; News clipping (Box 2, Folder 90)
  - Item 1: Farah Closing and Boycott, 1977; News clipping (Box 2, Folder 90)
    San Francisco Evening News. April 7, 1977
  - Item 2: Stockholder Challenge Of Stevens Spurs Protest To Methodist Unit, 1977; News clipping (Box 2, Folder 90)
    Michigan Christian Advocate. April 7, 1977
  - Item 3: Global Ministries Officers Advocate Collective Bargaining At J. P. Stevens Textile Firm, 1977; News clipping (Box 2, Folder 90)
    Zion's Herald. April 1977
- The Struggle Over Labor Law Refrom, 1978; News clipping (Box 2, Folder 91)
  Sunday News Journal. April 2, 1978
- Publisher's Notebook, 1978; News clipping (Box 2, Folder 92)
  Roanoke Rapids Herald. April 2, 1978
- Three Articles from various newspapers, 1977; News clipping (Box 2, Folder 93)
  - Item 1: Keeping Up With the Times, 1977; News clipping (Box 2, Folder 93)
    Vineland Times Journal. April 12, 1977
  - Item 2: Human Rights Key Issue in Union Struggle At J. P. Stevens, 1977; News clipping (Box 2, Folder 93)
    Labor World. April 22, 1977
  - Item 3: Justice Calls for Boycott of J. P. Stevens Prof Products, 1977; News clipping (Box 2, Folder 93)
    North Adams Transcript. April 15, 1977
- Three Articles from various newspapers, 1977; News clipping (Box 2, Folder 94)
  - Item 1: Blue-Collar Views: Labor Will Bring South Into Union, 1977; News clipping (Box 2, Folder 94)
    Chicago Tribune. April 5, 1977
  - Item 2: ACTWU Official Talks About OSHA Citation Action By Stevens, 1977; News clipping (Box 2, Folder 94)
    Roanoke Rapids Herald. April 12, 1977
  - Item 3: Boycott Vote Splits Coop Candidates, 1977; News clipping (Box 2, Folder 94)
    Harvard Crimson. April 16, 1977
- Labor News Conference: Program 52, Series 16, 1977; News clipping (Box 2, Folder 95)
  News From the AFL-CIO. April 13, 1977
- Title not included in photocopy. There is a widespread belief that North Carolina is the most enlightened state in the South, 1977; News clipping (Box 2, Folder 96)
  The Los Angeles Citizen. April 25, 1977
- Stevens Boycott Drive Launched: 'Textile War' Reaches Detroit, 1977; News clipping (Box 2, Folder 97)
  The Detroit News. April 20, 1977
- Three Articles from various newspapers, 1977; News clipping (Box 2, Folder 98)
  - Item 1: Stevens Witness Cross-Examined, 1977; News clipping (Box 2, Folder 98)
    Roanoke Rapids Herald. April 14, 1977
  - Item 2: ACTWU Asks Students' Help, 1977; News clipping (Box 2, Folder 98)
    Upper Sandusky Chief- Union. April 16, 1977
  - Item 3: Stevens Official Says ACTWU Knew Of Respirator Program, 1977; News clipping (Box 2, Folder 98)
    Roanoke Rapids Herald. April 21, 1977
- Princeton Club Cancels Talk By Whitney Stevens, 1977; News clipping (Box 2, Folder 99)
  Daily News Record. April 22, 1977
- Two Articles from the Charleston News and Courier, 1977; News clipping (Box 2, Folder 100)
  - Item 1: The New South, Old North Axis, 1977; News clipping (Box 2, Folder 100)
    Charleston News and Courier. April 21, 1977
  - Item 2: J. P. Stevens Actions Smack Of Civil Rights Tactics, 1977; News clipping (Box 2, Folder 100)
    Charleston News and Courier. April 20, 1977
- Stevens-ACTWU Fight Mars Mfrs. Hanover Meeting, 1977; News clipping (Box 2, Folder 101)
  Daily News Record. April 25, 1977
- Two Articles from The Detroit News, 1977; News clipping (Box 2, Folder 102)
  - Item 1: Unions Realize They Must Move to Regain Popularity, 1977; News clipping (Box 2, Folder 102)
    The Detroit News. April 25, 1977
  - Item 2: Brown Lung, 1977; News clipping (Box 2, Folder 102)
    Probably from The Detroit News. April 25, 1977
- What Situs Taught the Unions, 1977; News clipping (Box 2, Folder 103)
  Business Week. April 11, 1977
- Labor vs. J. P. Stevens: Songs and '60s Activism, 1977; News clipping (Box 2, Folder 104)
  The Charlotte Observer. April 18, 1977
- Spokesman Tells Group J. P. Stevens Fair With Union, 1977; News clipping (Box 2, Folder 105)
  Kinston Free Press. April 20, 1977
- Two Articles from the Greenville News, 1977; News clipping (Box 2, Folder 106)
  - Item 1: Hourly Workers: Stevens Plants Increase Wages, 1977; News clipping (Box 2, Folder 106)
    Greenville News. April 27, 1977
  - Item 2: Greenville Key to Stevens Campaign, 1977; News clipping (Box 2, Folder 106)
    Greenville News. April 29, 1977
- Social Justice in the South: Stake of Black Workers Cited In Struggle Against J. P. Stevens, 1977; News clipping (Box 2, Folder 107)
  AFL-CIO News. April 23, 1977
- Cause of Brown Lung: OSHA Proposal on Cotton Dust 'Grossly Inadequate', 1977; News clipping (Box 3, Folder 1)
  Press Associates. May 9, 1977
- The Crusade Against 14(b), 1977; News clipping (Box 3, Folder 2)
  The IUE News. May 1977
- The Sweatshop, 1977-style: Stevens v.s Justice, News clipping (Box 3, Folder 3)
  The Texas Observer. May 20, 1977
- Nationwide Boycott of J. P. Stevens Underway, News clipping (Box 3, Folder 4)
  Bakery and Confectionery Workers' International Union of America
- ACTW Urges Wage Hike of 15% in Mills, 1977; News clipping (Box 3, Folder 5)
  Daily News Record. May 2, 1977
- The Case for Labor Law Reform, 1977; News clipping (Box 3, Folder 6)
  New York Teacher Magazine. May 29, 1977
- Blue-Collar Views: Workers Caught in Company's Web, 1977; News clipping (Box 3, Folder 7)
  Chicago Tribune. May 31, 1977
- Washington & Business: A 'Pragmatic' Stance on Free Trade, 1977; News clipping (Box 3, Folder 8)
  The New York Times. June 2, 1977
- 7 Bishops Urge Stevens to Let Workers Organize, 1977; News clipping (Box 3, Folder 9)
  The New York Times. June 6, 1977
- Stevens to Bishops: Would Welcome More ACTW Talks, 1977; News clipping (Box 3, Folder 10)
  Daily News Record. June 6, 1977
- Organizing the South: Labor Calls J. P. Stevens Key Barrier, 1977; News clipping (Box 3, Folder 11)
  The Washington Post. June 7, 1977
- Bishops Offer Aid In Stevens Fight, May Join Boycott, 1977; News clipping (Box 3, Folder 12)
- Two Articles from the Mountian Eagle and the New Milford Times, 1977; News clipping (Box 3, Folder 13)
  - Item 1: Religious Groups Back J. P. Stevens Boycott, 1977; News clipping (Box 3, Folder 13)
    Mountain Eagle. June 23, 1977
  - Item 2: J. P. Stevens Controversy: 'Canning' Shocks Employees, 1977; News clipping (Box 3, Folder 13)
    New Milford Times. June 30, 1977
- Stevens Spokesman Says Companies Don't Move To Punish Employees, 1977; News clipping (Box 3, Folder 14)
- Two Articles from the New Milford Times and The Pittsburgh Press, 1977; News clipping (Box 3, Folder 15)
  - Item 1: Case Pending Before Labor Board: Union Enters Dispute to Defend Employee, 1977; News clipping (Box 3, Folder 15)
  - Item 2: Textile Firm, Union Debate Labor Tactics, 1977; News clipping (Box 3, Folder 15)
    The Pittsburgh Press. June 14, 1977
- The J. P. Stevens Connection: Why North Carolina Trails the Nation in Wages and Workers Who Are Unionized, 1977; News clipping (Box 3, Folder 16)
  Typographical Journal. July 22, 1977
- Reverand King, Sr. Speaks On J. P. Stevens Workers Effort, 1977; News clipping (Box 3, Folder 17)
  Labor Beacon. July 1, 1977
- A Throwback to Yesteryear? Labor Boycotts Textile Giant, 1977; News clipping (Box 3, Folder 18)
  Duluth News Tribune. July 5, 1977
- J. P. Stevens Ignores Roanoke Rapids Union, 1977; News clipping (Box 3, Folder 19)
  Racine Labor. July 8, 1977
- Three Articles from various newspapers, 1977; News clipping (Box 3, Folder 20)
- Long-Sufferers to Back Labor Law Reform, 1977; News clipping (Box 3, Folder 21)
  The Washington Star. July 19, 1977
  - Item 1: A Plea For Labor, 1977; News clipping (Box 3, Folder 21)
    Chicago Sun Times. July 14, 1977
  - Item 2: Jobless Blacks A Time Bomb, Scott Warns, 1977; News clipping (Box 3, Folder 21)
    The Atlanta Journal. August 15, 1977
  - Item 3: J. P. Stevens Answers Charges On the Unionization of Plants, 1977; News clipping (Box 3, Folder 21)
    Catholic Weekly. July 17, 1977
- Labor Boycotts J. P. Stevens, 1977; News clipping (Box 3, Folder 22)
  Calumet Day. July 20, 1977
- Two Articles from various newspapers, 1977; News clipping (Box 3, Folder 23)
  - Item 1: Rabbis Back Boycott, 1977; News clipping (Box 3, Folder 23)
    Minneapolis, MN. July 22, 1977
  - Item 2: A Sign of Desperation, 1977; News clipping (Box 3, Folder 23)
    Anderson Independent. July 30, 1977
- NLRB Dismisses Charge vs. Stevens, 1977; News clipping (Box 3, Folder 24)
  South Boston News and Record. July 26, 1977
- Unions Drawing Bead On Textile Industry, 1977; News clipping (Box 3, Folder 25)
  Columbia Record. July 27, 1977
- Labor Law Reform Drive Opens In Congress, 1977; News clipping (Box 3, Folder 26)
  Kentucky Labor News. July 30, 1977
- Labor Unions: The Battle Is On For The Southern Worker, 1977; News clipping (Box 3, Folder 27)
  The Charlotte News. July 30, 1977
- What is At Stake in the Stevens-Unin Struggle? A Statement By Fourteen Southern Ministers, News clipping (Box 3, Folder 28)
- The Battle: Union, Stevens Throw Men, Money Into Struggle, 1977; News clipping (Box 3, Folder 29)
  The Charlotte News. August 1, 1977
- House Hearings On Labor Law Reform, 1977; News clipping (Box 3, Folder 30)
  The Charlotte Observer. August 10, 1977
- Two Articles from the Shreveport Journal and The Detroit Free Press, 1977; News clipping (Box 3, Folder 31)
  - Item 1: Worker Protection Plan, 1977; News clipping (Box 3, Folder 31)
    Shreveport Journal. August 9, 1977
  - Item 2: J. P. Stevens Fires Back at Labor, 1977; News clipping (Box 3, Folder 31)
    The Detroit Free Press. August 9, 1977
- J. P. Stevens Workers Testify at Thompson Panel Hearings, 1977; News clipping (Box 3, Folder 32)
  Trenton Evening Times. August 9, 1977
- Dixie Blacklist: Textile Workers Relate Job Fears, 1977; News clipping (Box 3, Folder 33)
  San Francisco Examiner. August 9, 1977
- Hearings Open With Charges Against JPS, 1977; News clipping (Box 3, Folder 34)
  Roanoke Rapids Daily Herald. August 9, 1977
- Southern Textile Workers: Tuesday Was Union's Day in Sun, 1977; News clipping (Box 3, Folder 35)
  The Atlanta Journal. August 10, 1977
- Textile Mill Closing Bitterness Recounted, 1977; News clipping (Box 3, Folder 36)
  Shreveport Journal. August 10, 1977
- Kannapolis: Town Belongs To Cannon, 1977; News clipping (Box 3, Folder 37)
  The Charlotte News. August 2, 1977
- Two Articles from The Charlotte News, 1977; News clipping (Box 3, Folder 38)
  - Item 1: Dowd: To Keep Union Out, Keep Employes Happy, 1977; News clipping (Box 3, Folder 38)
    The Charlotte News. August 4, 1977
  - Item 2: Hoyman: Firms Want Profits, Not Higher Wages, 1977; News clipping (Box 3, Folder 38)
- Two Articles from The Chicago Tribune and the Catholic Weekly, 1977; News clipping (Box 3, Folder 39)
  - Item 1: Unions 'Devil's Tool,' U.S. Labor Panel Told, 1977; News clipping (Box 3, Folder 39)
    Chicago Tribune. August 10, 1977
  - Item 2: J. P. Stevens Answers Charges On the Unionization of Plants, 1977; News clipping (Box 3, Folder 39)
- Two Articles from The Detroit Free Press and the Daily Commercial News., 1977; News clipping (Box 3, Folder 40)
  - Item 1: J. P. Stevens Union Feud Carried to House Hearing, 1977; News clipping (Box 3, Folder 40)
    The Detroit Free Press. August 10, 1977
  - Item 2: A Charge That All U.S. Workers Heading For Unionism, 1977; News clipping (Box 3, Folder 40)
    Daily Commercial News. August 9, 1977
- Three Articles from various newspapers, 1977; News clipping (Box 3, Folder 41)
  - Item 1: Labor Relations Reform Backed, 1977; News clipping (Box 3, Folder 41)
    Newark Star-Ledger. August 18, 1977
  - Item 2: J. P. Stevens Union Feud Carried to House Hearing, 1977; News clipping (Box 3, Folder 41)
  - Item 3: J. P. Stevens Fires Back at Labor, 1977; News clipping (Box 3, Folder 41)
- Two Articles from the Washington Post and the Richmond Times-Dispatch, 1977; News clipping (Box 3, Folder 42)
  - Item 1: J. P. Stevens Guard Allegedly Threatened Union Organizer, 1977; News clipping (Box 3, Folder 42)
    The Washington Post. August 10, 1977
  - Item 2: Stevens Workers Split Over Union, 1977; News clipping (Box 3, Folder 42)
    Richmond Times- Dispatch. August 10, 1977
- J. P. Stevens Blasted in Congressional Hearing, 1977; News clipping (Box 3, Folder 43)
  This Week. August 11, 1977
- How to Stonewall Southern Style, 1977; News clipping (Box 3, Folder 44)
  Herald American. August 13, 1977
- J. P. Stevens Union-Busting Strengthens Reform Drive, 1977; News clipping (Box 3, Folder 45)
  AFL-CIO News. August 13, 1977
- We'll Take Jobs, You Keep Unions, 1977; News clipping (Box 3, Folder 46)
  La Grange News. August 15, 1977
- A New Twist: 'Whipping Boy' Strikes Back, 1977; News clipping (Box 3, Folder 47)
  Southern Textile News. August 15, 1977
- Spotlight On J. P. Stevens: House Panel in Roanoke Rapids Hears of Threats, Intimidation, 1977; News clipping (Box 3, Folder 48)
  Press Associates. August 15, 1977
- J. P. Stevens Gets Military Contracts, 1977; News clipping (Box 3, Folder 49)
  The News and Observer. August 17, 1977
- Battery of Unfair Practice Charges Hit J. P. Stevens, 1977; News clipping (Box 3, Folder 50)
  Labor News. August 18, 1977
- The Mills, and Unions, 1977; News clipping (Box 3, Folder 51)
  The New York Times. August 20, 1977
- Boycotts, Courts, Workers: Textile Union, Mill Fight on All Fronts, 1977; News clipping (Box 3, Folder 52)
  Detroit Free Press. August 21, 1977
- Union Controversy Discussed: Textile Tour Reactions Mixed, 1977; News clipping (Box 3, Folder 53)
  Anderson Independent. August 25, 1977
- Stevens Net Drops 27% in 3rd Quarter, 1977; News clipping (Box 3, Folder 54)
  Daily News Record. August 25, 1977
- We Take Issue With ACLU's Objections, 1977; News clipping (Box 3, Folder 55)
  Sanford Herald. August 6, 1977
- The Union Victory, 1977; News clipping (Box 3, Folder 56)
  Courier Record. August 11, 1977
- J. P. Stevens: It Helps Labor's Cause, 1977; News clipping (Box 3, Folder 57)
  The Charlotte Observer. September 4, 1977
- The Environment: Part Of South's Notion Of Life, 1977; News clipping (Box 3, Folder 58)
  The Charlotte Observer. September 19, 1977
- Union Fringe Benefit: Free Day Care, 1977; News clipping (Box 3, Folder 59)
  The Milwaukee Journal. September 25, 1977
- Labor Dispute: Decision Finds Firm In Violation, 1977; News clipping (Box 3, Folder 60)
  September 29, 1977.
- Where Kleagles Dare, 1977; News clipping (Box 3, Folder 61)
  National Lampoon. September 1977